CHIKA AULIA ZAHWA

Jakarta Timur, DKI Jakarta | 085772634680 | chikaauliazahwa11@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/chikaaulia11 | github.com/chikaauli | portfolio-chikaaul

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Fresh graduate majoring in Information Engineering and have experience in a certified independent study internship (MSIB) at Kampus Merdeka. I do front-end web development and full stack web developer to develop websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various frameworks like Laravel and React JS. With strong curiosity, I like to learn something new in my life, especially about IT and programming language.

EDUCATION

STT Terpadu Nurul Fikri - Depok, Indonesia

Bachelor in information Engineering (GPA: 3.94/4.00)

Sep 2020 - Sep 2024

EXPERIENCES

PT Impactbyte Teknologi Edukasi | (Independent Study From Kampus Merdeka) Front-End Web Development

Feb 2023 - Jun 2023

Skilvul is an online vocational training and certification platform for digital skills with a mission to build job-ready digital talent.

- Collaborated with the team to design UI/UX design.
- Implement design and create website using React JS Vite.
- Worked with back-end developers to seamlessly integrate user-facing elements with server-side logic.
- Developed and maintained high-performance, responsive front-end web applications.
- Optimized web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

PT Nurul Fikri Cipta Inovasi | (Independent Study From Kampus Merdeka) Full-stack Web Developer

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

NF Academy is an institution in the field of IT (Information Technology) education and training.

- Collaborate on projects with a team using Github.
 - Design a data storage (database).
 - Implement design and build APIs using Php Laravel.
 - Deploy and hosting website that have been finished into webmin.
 - Enhanced communication and collaboration skills within a diverse team.

Badan Kepegawaian Negara (BKN RI) General Administration

Okt 2018 - Dec 2018

BKN RI is an Indonesian government agency that manages and develops human resources in the government sector.

- Handling phone calls and receiving guests.
- Taking minutes.
- Delivering letters.
- Writing expedition books and writing position books.

FEATURED PROJECTS

Serrum - Platform Remedial (Front-End Web Development) - A React web app that offers knowledge about art and literacy through art understanding, discussion about millennial art, and graphic printing practice.

Web Streaming Film - NFlix (Full-stack Web Developer) - A streaming platform with a daily updated collection of the latest movies and series, featuring unlimited viewing on any device, and a responsive design using Laravel and Bootstrap.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Front-End Web Development Skilvul #Tech4Impact (MSIB Batch 4), 30 June 2023
- Demo Day Skilvul #Tech4Impact Front-End & Back-End Web Development, 27 June 2023
- Full-stack Web Developer Academy NF Computer (MSIB Batch 3), 31 December 2022

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Git & Github
- HTML 5 dan CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React JS

- Ms. Office (Ms. Word, Ms. Excel, Ms. Powerpoint)
- Google (Google Docs, Google Spreadsheets, Google Slides)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Indonesian (Native Proficiency)
- English (Beginner Intermediate)